David Dunsford collection of ABC and CBS network television press releases
National Audio-Visual Conservation Center, Library of Congress, Library of Congress
David Dunsford collection of ABC and CBS network television press releases 1962-1970
Dunsford, David A.
4,200 items; 5 linear feet (12 boxes)
Moving Image Research Center, National Audio-Visual Conservation Center, Library of Congress, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
This collection contains photocopies of original press releases released by the American television networks ABC and CBS between June 11, 1962 and July 4, 1970. The original press releases were collected by David A. Dunsford. The press releases pertain to news programs, television specials, documentaries, movies of the week, religious programs, variety shows, talk shows, soap operas, news programming, dramas, and situation comedies broadcast by ABC and CBS.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Dunsford, David A.
Organizations
ABC Television Network; CBS Television Network
Subjects
Television programs--Marketing.; Television programs--United States--1960-1970.
Form/Genre
Photocopies.; Press releases.
Collection Acquisition
The collection was acquired from David Dunsford in 2015.
Additions
No further additions to the collection are expected.
Access Restrictions
The David A. Dunsford Collection is open for research. Contact a reference librarian in the Moving Image Research Center, National Audio-Visual Conservation Center, Library of Congress, Library of Congress, Washington, DC, 20540-4690; (202) 707-8572.
Organizational Note
The American Broadcasting Company (ABC) was founded in 1943 from the assets of the National Broadcasting Company (NBC) Blue Network. Television network operations commenced in 1948.
The Columbia Broadcasting System (CBS) was founded in 1929 as a radio broadcasting network. Television operations began in 1931 with the establishment of experimental station W2XAB in New York City. W2XAB received a commercial license as WCBW (later renamed WCBS) in 1941. Television network operations commenced in 1948.
Scope and Content Note
This collection contains photocopies of original press releases released by the American television networks ABC and CBS between June 11, 1962 and July 4, 1970. The original press releases were collected by David A. Dunsford. The press releases pertain to news programs, television specials, documentaries, movies of the week, religious programs, variety shows, talk shows, soap operas, news programming, dramas, and situation comedies broadcast by ABC and CBS.
Collection Arrangement
The collection is arranged in 2 series:
Series 1: ABC Press Releases, 1962-10-02--1970-07-04
Series 2: CBS Press Releases, 1962-06-11--1970-05-19
Records are organized by network (ABC, CBS) and alphabetically thereunder. Press releases pertaining to each individual program, special, or series are organized in distinct folders and indicate date or date range of press releases in parenthesis.
Container List
- Series 1. ABC Press Releases, 1962-10-02--1970-07-04
  - ABC Movie of the Week, 1969-09-23--1970-03-17 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - Agony of Vietnam (Special), 1965-08-25 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Alcoa Preview (Specials), 1965-02-04--1965-03-14 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Alice in Wonderland OR What’s a Nice Kid Like You Doing in a Place Like This (Special), 1966-03-30 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Among the Paths to Eden (Special), 1967-12-17 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Amos Burke, Secret Agent, 1965-09-15--1966-01-12 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Anatomy of Pop: The Music Explosion (Special), 1966-02-15 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - ...And Debbie Makes Six, 1968-03-07 (Box-folder 1/8)
  - Around the Beatles (Special), 1964-11-15 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Assault (Special), 1966-04-19 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - Avengers, 1966-03-28--1969-04-21 (Box-folder 1/11)
  - Baron, 1966-01-20--1966-05-05 (Box-folder 1/12)
  - Bewitched, 1964-09-17--1966-12-29 (Box-folder 1/13)
  - Bewitched, 1967-01-05--1969-12-18 (Box-folder 1/14)
  - Beatles at Shea Stadium (Special), 1967-01-10 (Box-folder 1/15)
  - Bing Crosby Show, 1964-09-14--1965-04-19 (Box-folder 1/16)
  - Blue Light, 1966-01-12--1966-05-18 (Box-folder 1/17)
  - Broadside, 1964-09-20--1965-05-02 (Box-folder 1/18)
  - Burke's Law (Second Season), 1964-09-16--1965-04-28 (Box-folder 1/19)
  - Carol Channing Specials, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 1/2-)
  - Comrade Soldier (Special), 1969-05-16 (Box-folder 1/21)
  - Comedy of Ernie Kovacs, 1968-04-09 (Box-folder 1/22)
  - Coach Bryant: Alabama's Bear (Special), 1967-10-23 (Box-folder 1/23)
  - Confrontation (Special, Army-McCarthy Hearings), 1968-04-05 (Box-folder 1/24)
  - Custer, 1967-09-06--1968-01-03 (Box-folder 1/25)
  - Dangerous Christmas of Red Riding Hood OR Wolf, Poor Wolf (Special), 1965-11-28 (Box-folder 2/1)
  - Daring American (Specials), 1964-09-10--1965-04-10 (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Dark Shadows (Premiere), 1966-06-27 (Box-folder 2/3)
  - Discovery, 1962-10-02--1965-12-26 (Box-folder 2/4)
  - Discovery, 1966-01-02--1969-12-28 (Box-folder 2/5)
  - Directions (Religious Series), 1964-10-04--1966-12-25 (Box-folder 2/6)
  - Directions (Religious Series), 1967-01-01--1969-12-28 (Box-folder 2/7)
  - Do Blondes Have More Fun (Special), 1967-08-28 (Box-folder 2/8)
  - Don Rickles Show, 1968-09-27--1969-01-31 (Box-folder 2/9)
  - Double Life of Henry Phyfe, 1966-01-13--1966-06-30 (Box-folder 2/10)
  - Elections '66, 1966-10-02--1966-10-30 (Box-folder 2/11)
  - Electric Showcase (Specials), 1964-1965 (Box-folder 2/12)
  - Everett Dirksen's Washington (Specials), 1968-01-22 (Box-folder 2/13)
  - F Troop, 1965-09-14--1967-04-06 (Box-folder 2/14)
  - Farmer's Daughter (Seasons 2, 3), 1964-09-18--1966-04-22 (Box-folder 2/15)
  - FBI, 1965-09-19--1969-12-28 (Box-folder 3/1)
  - FDR, 1965-01-08--1965-07-23 (Box-folder 3/2)
  - Felony Squad, 1966-09-12--1969-01-31 (Box-folder 3/3)
  - Folk Gospel Music Festival (Special), 1969-09-16 (Box-folder 3/4)
  - Fugitive, 1964-09-15--1967-08-29 (Box-folder 3/5)
  - Garrison's Gorillas, 1967-09-05--1968-03-12 (Box-folder 3/6)
  - Garry Moore's People Poll (Special), 1966-02-04 (Box-folder 3/7)
  - Go!!! (Special), 1967-04-23 (Box-folder 3/8)
  - Grambling College: 100 Yards to Glory (Special), 1968-07-30 (Box-folder 3/9)
  - Great Dollar Robber: Can We Arrest Inflation? (Special), 1969-12-15 (Box-folder 3/10)
  - Great Mating Game (Special), 1968-04-08 (Box-folder 3/11)
  - Green Hornet, 1966-09-09--1967-03-17 (Box-folder 3/12)
  - Guide to the Swinging Bachelor (Special), 1968-12-10 (Box-folder 3/13)
  - Holiday on Ice (Specials), 1966-05-14, 1967-09-24 (Box-folder 3/14)
  - Hollywood Palace, 1964-07-11--1965-12-25 (Box-folder 3/15)
  - Hollywood Palace, 1966-01-01--1966-12-31 (Box-folder 3/16)
  - Hollywood Palace, 1967-01-07--1967-12-26 (Box-folder 3/17)
  - Hollywood Palace, 1968-01-02--1968-12-28 (Box-folder 3/18)
  - Hollywood Palace, 1969-01-04--1970-02-07 (Box-folder 3/19)
  - Jack Jones on the Move (Special), 1966-04-05 (Box-folder 3/20)
  - Jimmy Dean Show, 1964-09-17--1966-04-01 (Box-folder 4/1)
  - Jimmy Durante Presents The Lennon Sisters Hour, 1969-09-26--1970-07-04 (Box-folder 4/2)
  - John F. Kennedy: His Two Worlds (Special), 1964-11-22 (Box-folder 4/3)
  - Killy Le Champion (Special), 1969-01-13 (Box-folder 4/4)
  - King Family, 1965-01-23--1966-01-08 (Box-folder 4/5)
  - Land of the Giants, 1968-09-22--1970-03-22 (Box-folder 4/6)
  - Last Laugh at the 60's (Special), 1970-01-08 (Box-folder 4/7)
  - Legend of Jesse James, 1965-09-13--1966-05-09 (Box-folder 4/8)
  - Masters of Pop: Innocence, Anarchy and Soul (Special), 1969-08-07 (Box-folder 4/9)
  - McHale's Navy (Seasons 3, 4), 1964-09-15--1966-04-12 (Box-folder 4/10)
  - Melina Mercouri's Greece (Special), 1965-05-03 (Box-folder 4/11)
  - Mickey, 1964-09-16--1965-01-06 (Box-folder 4/12)
  - Middle East War (Special), 1967-06-08 (Box-folder 4/13)
  - Milton Berle Show, 1966-09-09--1967-01-06 (Box-folder 4/14)
  - Music Scene, 1969-09-22--1970-01-12 (Box-folder 4/15)
  - Monroes, 1966-09-07--1967-03-15 (Box-folder 4/16)
  - Monte Carlo... C'est La Rose (Special), 1966-03-06 (Box-folder 4/17)
  - Movie Night Specials, 1967-10-22--1968-03-03 (Box-folder 4/18)
  - Mr. Deeds Goes to Town, 1969-09-26--1970-01-16 (Box-folder 4/19)
  - Mr. Dickens of London (Special), 1967-12-12 (Box-folder 4/20)
  - New People, 1969-09-22--1970-01-12 (Box-folder 4/21)
  - Now Generation (Special), 1968-03-06 (Box-folder 4/22)
  - Nurses: Crisis in Medicine (Special), 1967-06-09 (Box-folder 4/23)
  - O.K. Crackerby!, 1965-09-16--1966-01-06 (Box-folder 4/24)
  - On Location with David L. Wolper's Production of the 'The Devil's Brigade' (Special), 1968-07-19 (Box-folder 4/25)
  - One More Time, 1968-04-08 (Box-folder 4/26)
  - One Night Stands, 1967-11-21 (Box-folder 4/27)
  - Operation: Entertainment, 1968-01-05--1969-01-31 (Box-folder 4/28)
  - Peyton Place, 1964-09-15--1966-12-28 (Box-folder 5/1)
  - Peyton Place, 1967-01-02--1969-06-02 (Box-folder 5/2)
  - Piccadilly Palace, 1967-05-20--1967-09-09 (Box-folder 5/3)
  - Pied Piper of Astroworld (Special), 1968-12-28 (Box-folder 5/4)
  - Politics '64: George Gobel, A Man Who... (Special), 1964-08-20 (Box-folder 5/5)
  - Pursuit of Excellence: The Vienna Boys Choir (Special), 1968-02-24 (Box-folder 5/6)
  - Rango, 1967-01-13--1967-05-05 (Box-folder 5/7)
  - Rat Patrol, 1966-09-12--1968-03-18 (Box-folder 5/8)
  - Riddle of the Mayan Caves (Special), 1969-05-09 (Box-folder 5/9)
  - Rise and Fall of the Third Reich (Specials), 1968-03-06--1968-03-08 (Box-folder 5/10)
  - Saga of Western Man (Documentary Specials), 1965-02-23--1969-05-08 (Box-folder 5/11)
  - Shephardes' Playe (Special), 1967-12-24 (Box-folder 5/12)
  - Science All Stars (Season 1), 1965-01-10--1965-04-25 (Box-folder 5/13)
  - Singers (Special, Gloria Loring, Aretha Franklin), 1968-05-11 (Box-folder 5/14)
  - That's Life, 1968-09-24--1969-04-01 (Box-folder 5/15)
  - Turn-On, 1969-02-05 (Box-folder 5/16)
  - What's It All About, World?, 1969-02-06--1969-05-01 (Box-folder 5/17)
- Series 2. CBS Press Releases, 1962-06-11--1970-05-19
  - 60 Minutes, 1968-09-24--1969-12-16 (Box-folder 6/1)
  - Adventure at the Jade Sea (Special), 1969-03-26 (Box-folder 6/2)
  - Ages of Man (Special), 1966-06-03, 1966-06-10 (Box-folder 6/3)
  - Alfred Hitchcock Hour, 1962-09-20--1964-06-05 (Box-folder 6/4)
  - And Many Shall Rejoice (Special), 1967-12-24 (Box-folder 6/5)
  - Ann-Margret Specials, 1968-12-01--1969-12-06 (Box-folder 6/6)
  - Armstrong Circle Theatre, 1962-07-05--1963-08-08 (Box-folder 6/7)
  - Armstrong Circle Theatre (Specials), 1968-1968 (Box-folder 6/8)
  - Arthur Godfrey Specials ( 1962-1963 Season) (Box-folder 6/9)
  - At the Drop of Another Hat (Special), 1967-12-18 (Box-folder 6/10)
  - Away We Go, 1967-06-03--1967-09-02 (Box-folder 6/11)
  - Barbra Streisand Specials, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 6/12)
  - Beverly Hillbillies, 1962-09-26--1965-12-29 (Box-folder 6/13)
  - Beverly Hillbillies, 1966-01-05--1969-12-31 (Box-folder 6/14)
  - Camera Three, 1964-01-05--1966-12-25 (Box-folder 6/15)
  - Camera Three, 1967-01-01--1969-12-28 (Box-folder 6/16)
  - Cara Williams Show, 1964-09-23--1965-04-21 (Box-folder 6/17)
  - Carol Burnett Presents The Jimmie Rodgers Show, 1969-06-16--1969-08-25 (Box-folder 6/18)
  - Carol Burnett Show, 1967-09-11--1969-12-29 (Box-folder 6/19)
  - Carol Burnett Specials, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 7/1)
  - Cavalcade of Amateurs (Special), 1965-03-28--1965-04-04 (Box-folder 7/2)
  - CBS Reports and CBS News Prime-Time Specials, 1962-06-21--1963-12-18 (Box-folder 7/3)
  - CBS Reports and CBS News Prime-Time Specials, 1964-01-08--1964-12-28 (Box-folder 7/4)
  - CBS Reports and CBS News Prime-Time Specials, 1965-01-04--1965-12-28 (Box-folder 7/5)
  - CBS Reports and CBS News Prime-Time Specials, 1966-01-11--1966-12-27 (Box-folder 7/6)
  - CBS Reports and CBS News Prime-Time Specials, 1967-01-03--1967-12-19 (Box-folder 7/7)
  - CBS Reports and CBS News Prime-Time Specials, 1968-01-02--1969-12-30 (Box-folder 7/8)
  - Charlie Brown/Peanuts Specials, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 8/1)
  - Coronet Blue, 1967-05-29--1967-09-04 (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Creative America (Special), 1963-03-17 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Daktari, 1966-01-11--1969-01-15 (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Defenders, 1962-09-15--1965-05-13 (Box-folder 8/5)
  - Diary of a Madman (Special), 1967-12-20 (Box-folder 8/6)
  - Dickens Chronicle (Special), 1963-02-13 (Box-folder 8/7)
  - Dionne Warwick Special... Souled Out, 1969-09-17 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Do You Know?, 1963-10-12--1964-04-25 (Box-folder 8/9)
  - Doctors and the Nurses, 1964-09-22--1965-05-11 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Dom DeLuise Show, 1968-05-01--1968-09-18 (Box-folder 8/11)
  - Dundee and the Culhane, 1967-09-06--1967-12-13 (Box-folder 8/12)
  - East Side/West Side, 1963-09-23--1964-04-27 (Box-folder 8/13)
  - Ed Sullivan Show 20th Anniversary Press kit, 1967-12-01--1967-12-31 (Box-folder 8/14)
  - Ed Sullivan Show, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 8/15)
  - Ed Sullivan Show, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 8/16)
  - Ed Sullivan Show, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 8/17)
  - Emperor's New Clothes (Special), 1967-09-04 (Box-folder 8/18)
  - Enchanted Isles (Special), 1969-01-22 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Entertainers, 1964-09-25--1965-03-27 (Box-folder 8/20)
  - Exceeding Great Joy, 1967-12-24 (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Exhibition: Contemporary American Painters (Special), 1963-03-10 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Fair Exchange (60 minute format: 1962-09-21--1962-12-28, 30 minute format: 1963-03-14--1963-06-13 ) (Box-folder 8/23)
  - Fanfare, 1965-06-19--1965-09-11 (Box-folder 8/24)
  - For the People, 1965-01-31--1965-05-09 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Four Dark Days (CBS News Special), 1964-11-22 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Fred Astaire Specials (Rebroadcasts), 1964-12-10, 1965-01-03, 1965-01-10 (Box-folder 9/3)
  - Garry Moore Show, 1962-06-12--1964-06-16, 1966-09-11--1967-01-08 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - General Electric True, 1962-09-30--1963-05-26 (Box-folder 9/5)
  - Gentle Ben, 1967-09-10--1969-04-27 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Gold Ring (Sports Special), 1966-08-05 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Gilligan's Island, 1964-09-26--1967-04-17 (Box-folder 9/8)
  - Gomer Pyle - USMC, 1964-09-25--1969-05-02 (Box-folder 9/9)
  - Good Morning World, 1967-09-05--1968-03-19 (Box-folder 9/10)
  - Green Acres, 1965-09-15--1969-12-27 (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Great Adventure, 1963-09-27--1964-05-01 (Box-folder 9/12)
  - Great Challenge (Season 6), 1963-02-03--1963-03-03 (Box-folder 9/13)
  - Hippodrome, 1966-07-05--1966-09-06 (Box-folder 9/14)
  - Hogan's Heroes, 1965-09-17--1969-12-26 (Box-folder 9/15)
  - Hollywood Talent Scouts, 1965-06-22--1966-06-20 (Box-folder 9/16)
  - Hour with Robert Goulet (Special), 1964-11-19 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Jean Arthur Show, 1966-09-12--1966-12-05 (Box-folder 9/18)
  - Jericho, 1966-09-15--1967-01-19 (Box-folder 9/19)
  - The Jo Stafford Show (Special), 1963-08-18 (Box-folder 9/20)
  - John Gary Show, 1966-06-22--1966-09-07 (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Judy Garland Show, 1963-09-29--1963-03-29 (Box-folder 9/22)
  - Juilliard Comes to Lincoln Center: A Dedication Concert (Special), 1969-10-26 (Box-folder 9/23)
  - Julie and Carol at Carnegie Hall (Special), 1962-06-11 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Keefe Brasselle's Variety Gardens (Special), 1962-09-18 (Box-folder 10/2)
  - Killy Style, 1968-01-05--1968-05-04 (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Lamp unto My Feet, 1964-01-05--1969-06-15 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Lancer, 1968-09-24--1970-05-19 (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Law and Lee Oswald (Special), 1963-12-29 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Leslie Uggams Show, 1969-09-28--1969-12-14 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Let the Desert Be Joyful (Special), 1966-12-24 (Box-folder 10/8)
  - Let's Go the the Fair! (Special), 1965-04-21 (Box-folder 10/9)
  - Liberace Show, 1969-07-08--1969-09-16 (Box-folder 10/10)
  - Lincoln Center Day (Specials), 1962-09-23, 1963-09-22, 1964-09-20 (Box-folder 10/11)
  - Lombardi (Special), 1968-09-15 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Look at Monaco with Princess Grace (Special), 1964-02-17 (Box-folder 10/13)
  - Look Up and Live, 1964-02-02--1966-12-18 (Box-folder 10/14)
  - Look Up and Live, 1967-01-15--1969-11-23 (Box-folder 10/15)
  - Mark Twain Tonight! (Special), 1967-03-06 (Box-folder 10/16)
  - Martin's Lie (Special), 1965-05-30 (Box-folder 10/17)
  - Meet the New Senators (Special), 1969-01-05 (Box-folder 10/18)
  - Memoirs: Sixty Years on the Firing Line (Arthur Krock Special), 1969-01-12 (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Michelob Hour of Excellence (Specials), 1965 (Box-folder 10/20)
  - Middle East Perspective: Can Peace Break Out? (Special), 1967-08-23 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Midsummer Night's Dream (Special), 1969-02-09 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Mission Impossible, 1966-09-17--1969-12-21 (Box-folder 10/23)
  - Mission to Mars: The Search for Life (Special), 1965-07-11 (Box-folder 10/24)
  - Mr. Broadway, 1964-09-26--1964-12-26 (Box-folder 10/25)
  - Mr. Terrific, 1967-01-09--1967-05-08 (Box-folder 10/26)
  - Mister Mayor, 1964-09-26--1965-09-18 (Box-folder 10/27)
  - Munsters, 1964-09-24--1966-05-12 (Box-folder 11/1)
  - My Living Doll, 1964-09-27--1965-03-17 (Box-folder 11/2)
  - My Favorite Martian, 1963-09-29--1966-05-08 (Box-folder 11/3)
  - National Geographic Society Specials, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Nato in Danger (Special), 1964-12-15 (Box-folder 11/5)
  - Natural History of Our World: The Time of Man (Special), 1969-09-18 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - New Phil Silvers Show, 1963-09-28--1964-04-25 (Box-folder 11/7)
  - Nurses: Crisis in Medicine (Special), 1962-09-27--1964-06-25 (Box-folder 11/8)
  - Nutcracker (Special), 1965-12-21 (Box-folder 11/9)
  - Of Black America (Specials), 1968-07-02--1968-09-02 (Box-folder 11/10)
  - On Broadway Tonight, 1964-07-08--1964-09-16, 1965-01-01--1965-03-05 (Box-folder 11/11)
  - Once Upon a Mattress (Special), 1964-06-03 (Box-folder 11/12)
  - One of a Kind, 1964-01-12--1964-03-29 (Box-folder 11/13)
  - Our Place, 1967-07-02--1967-09-03 (Box-folder 11/14)
  - Our Private World, 1965-05-05--1965-09-10 (Box-folder 11/15)
  - Petticoat Junction, 1963-09-24--1966-12-27 (Box-folder 11/16)
  - Petticoat Junction, 1967-01-03--1970-04-04 (Box-folder 11/17)
  - Pinocchio (Special), 1967-02-13 (Box-folder 11/18)
  - Portrait, 1963-01-30--1963-09-29 (Box-folder 11/19)
  - Pro Football - The Story of the NFL (Special), 1962-09-20 (Box-folder 11/20)
  - Pistols 'N' Petticoats, 1966-09-17--1967-03-11 (Box-folder 11/21)
  - Queen and I, 1968-01-16--1968-05-01 (Box-folder 11/22)
  - Reckoning, 1963-06-26--1963-09-18 (Box-folder 11/23)
  - Red Skelton Hour, 1962-09-25--1964-12-29 (Box-folder 11/24)
  - Red Skelton Hour, 1965-01-05--1967-12-19 (Box-folder 12/1)
  - Red Skelton Hour, 1968-01-09--1970-04-07 (Box-folder 12/2)
  - Religious Specials, 1962-12-27--1969-12-29 (Box-folder 12/3)
  - Remedy for a Riot (Special), 1968-03-03 (Box-folder 12/4)
  - Reporter, 1964-09-25--1964-12-25 (Box-folder 12/5)
  - Road Signs on the Merry-Go-Round (Special), 1968-01-07 (Box-folder 12/6)
  - Road to Button Bay (Special), 1964-09-24 (Box-folder 12/7)
  - Shane, 1966-09-10--1966-12-31 (Box-folder 12/8)
  - Sid Caesar, Imogene Coca, Carl Reiner, Howard Morris Special, 1967-04-05 (Box-folder 12/9)
  - Simon and Garfunkel (Special), 1969-11-30 (Box-folder 12/10)
  - Singers (Special, Jack Jones, Michele Lee), 1969-09-08 (Box-folder 12/11)
  - Smothers Brothers Comedy Hour, 1967-02-05--1969-04-06 (Box-folder 12/12)
  - Slattery's People, 1964-09-21--1965-11-26 (Box-folder 12/13)
  - Spotlight, 1967-06-27--1967-08-29 (Box-folder 12/14)
  - Steve Allen Comedy Hour, 1967-06-14--1967-08-16 (Box-folder 12/15)
  - Suspense, 1964-03-25--1964-06-17 (Box-folder 12/16)
  - Twentieth Century, 1962-07-01--1966-09-25 (Box-folder 12/17)
  - Twilight Zone, 1963-01-05--1963-05-23 (Box-folder 12/18)
  - World War I, 1964-09-22--1965-04-18 (Box-folder 12/19)
  - Young People's Concerts (Leonard Bernstein Specials), 1962-11-21--1970-03-29 (Box-folder 12/20)
  - Zoorama, 1965-04-18--1965-09-05 (Box-folder 12/21)